let me
tell you a story it's about a child
a dreamer that wasn't too sure she ever
wanted to grow up
she spent her days at the trees speaking
to them about her plans to be a great
explorer
[Music]
the child built fairy houses and
sketched the gnomes she spotted in the
grasses
she told stories to the fishers secrets
to the starlings
marveled at the night sky and would
return home
with very muddy boots
[Music]
one day she happened upon a portal to a
wondrous land
a world afflicted by eternal winter
where the homely beavers and sly foxes
feared to wander in the open lest
vicious wolves enslave them to the
service of a malevolent
queen
[Music]
do
when the child returned to the human
world she was different
there was a hunger insider a desperate
need for new and fantastical tales
as the seasons changed and she grew
older she made new acquaintances
friends that would hold her hand through
the tribulations of growing up
some of them were real and some were in
her books
she had no choice but to eventually
enter the land of big people
and at times she felt very alone
but no matter how dark things seemed her
books could take her to places of hope
and warmth and sweetness through her
journey she found other people that were
quite similar to her
and that her story was shared by many
and that
made all the difference do you love
to read i do and so it made sense that i
dedicate a video to one of my greatest
passions
and of course i included some recipes of
some cozy drinks i might prepare
for a day of reading i was recently
recommended lavender hot chocolate
and i simply had to try the recipe it
turns out to be absolutely
[Music]
delicious
i am not a fast reader nor do i think i
have particularly good taste
but it has always benefited me greatly
in more ways than one
reading is known to keep your memory
sharp reduce stress
and improve your brain connectivity plus
reading about the stories of other
people real or fictional
challenges us to empathize and
understand those from different cultures
and backgrounds
it also makes us question ourselves
i am reticent to give recommendations
since each person's taste is different
however i thought i'd share some of my
personal favorites
[Music]
i love old books on history that teach
me about daily life in the past
also books on nature herbs and wild
crafting which i will link in the
description
i love thrilling dramas full of danger
and secrets
and i will always have a penchant for
children's stories
for example when i was 9 years old i
fell in love with a little mouse named
despero
who desperately wanted to be a knight he
taught me that you are who you believe
yourself to be
and that comes with the responsibility
of defining yourself by your strengths
instead of your weaknesses as a teacher
i also love
children's books and have so many
favorites i was recently gifted this
beautifully illustrated book on mother
[Music]
nature
do
[Music]
so
finding a good story one that makes your
heart race and your mind buzz with new
thoughts and imaginings is a joy that i
can compare to few things in this world
the greatest gift it gives me besides
transporting me into a story
is that it rejuvenates my mind and
brings about a wholesome sense of peace
reducing my heart rate and racing
thoughts and reminding me that here
right now i have control my worries and
fears do not need to weigh
so heavy on my shoulders and after a
night of dreaming and storytelling
things will inevitably be brighter in
the morning
i know that reading isn't everyone's
preferred pastime
and i would love to hear what you in
particular do to relax
or share some of your favorite books as
you
already know i am someone who has many
hobbies
and i find that the process of slowing
down and concentrating on a task
reading or otherwise gives me a sense of
strength
that in a world full of distractions and
stimulation
i can choose to take a deep breath and
[Music]
reset